question_data = [
    {"category": "General Knowledge",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "French is an official language in Canada.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Musicals & Theatres", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the play Oedipus Rex, Oedipus kills his father due to jealousy in loving his mother.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In 2016, the United Kingdom voted to stay in the EU.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Studio Ghibli is a Japanese animation studio responsible for the films: "
                 "'Wolf Children' and 'The Boy and the Beast'.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Sports", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Peyton Manning retired after winning Super Bowl XLIX.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Solid Snake is actually a clone from the DNA of Big Boss in the Metal Gear Solid series&#039; history.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Rebecca Chambers does not appear in any Resident Evil except for the original Resident Evil and the Gamecube remake.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Board Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "There is a Donald Trump Board Game, which was made in 1989.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon, Arbok evolves into Seviper.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Adolf Hitler was tried at the Nuremberg trials.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Rabbits can see what&#039;s behind themselves without turning their heads.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Vietnam&#039;s national flag is a red star in front of a yellow background.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
